

# Kazeem Amuzat

Front-End Developer

- Quarters Extension, Jemilu Lion Street, Kuje, FCT, Abuja, Nigeria., +234 903101

#### Education

B.Tech (Hons.) Mathematics "4.03/5.0"

Jan 2010 - Mar 2016

Ondo State University of Science and Technology, Okitipupa

**Mathematics** 

**JavaScript Maters Course** 

Dec 2020 - Dec 2021

OGTECH NETWORKS LTD, FCT., Abuja

JavaScript

**REACTJS** Dec 2021 - May 2022

UDEMY, Online

JavaSript Library for bulding user interfaces

# **Employment**

Front-End Developer Jun 2021 - Present

K-Devs System Solutions

Software Developer Intern Jun 2021 - Nov 2021

K-Devs System Solutions, Lagos

Lead HR/Project Interface Coordinator Nov 2019 - Feb 2021

Intertech Systems Ltd, Lagos

HR Executive Jan 2018 - Oct 2019

Intertech Systems Ltd, Lagos

### **Profile**

I am a FrontEnd Engineer with experience in JavaScript and ReactJs Technologies, I have ditched out application development using the aforementioned stacks with experience in project management (PM). I am currently working at K-Devs System Solutions.

#### Courses

React - The Complete Guide (inclusive of Hooks, React Router and Redux)

May 2022

Dec 2021

React Js methodologies as JavaScript library for user interfaces.

JavaScript
JavaScript Methodologies.

Place of birth

Personal details

lwo

Driver's license GGE61612AA11

Date of birth

July 30th, 1988

Gender

Male

Nationality Nigerian

Website

my-news-appbeta.vercel.app

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/kazeem-amuzat-0820b113b

#### Skills

Time management
Organizational skills
Communication skills
Teamwork Conceptual skills
Creative thinking Decision
making Problem solving
Leadership

# Languages

English Language and Yoruba Language

## Internships

#### Software Developer Intern

Jun 2021 - Nov 2021

K-Devs System Solutions, Lagos

I contributed in coding new mid-features and app testing for eduTech application which contributes positively in achieving the business goal.

### Certificates

React JS May 2022

React JS methodologies.

JavaScript Dec 2021

JavaScript Methodologies.

Professional Diploma in Project Aug 2020

Management & Leadership Training -

**SHAW ACADEMY** 

Professional Diploma in Project Management & Leadership Training – SHAW ACADEMY

Workforce Collaboration and Oct 2020

Development

Workforce Collaboration and Development - YALI NETWORK

Advanced Strategic Human Resources Jun 2018

Management

Advanced Strategic Human Resources Management –

**CLARIONTTECH SERVICES** 

Project Management Proficiency (PMP) Jul 2017

Project Management Proficiency (PMP) – PALMSLAND CONSULT,

**NIGERIA** 

# **Projects**

Among several others, I built a news app that dives into the concept of API and associated endpoints consumptions. It centers, majorly, around admin usability while testing the dexterity of the developer in resolving issues programmatically and the ability to execute route implementations.

https://github.com/amuzatk/My-news-app

### References

References available upon request.

#### **Hobbies**

Reading, Traveling,
 Computer Simulation
 Games

### Qualities

■ Creative, energetic, resourceful and productive professional with strong ability to recognize needs, opportunities and possibilities and to take quick and necessary steps when required.